(Leonard:)-Okay, so Kripke played a joke on you.
-It wasn't funny.
[IN NORMAL VOICE]
I thought it was funny.
(Penny:)-Raj.
-You laughed.
(Sheldon:)Did you laugh?
(Leonard:)I fell on the floor.
(Leonard:)All right, he got you.
You can get him back.
(Sheldon:)-I refuse to sink to his level.
-You can't sink.
(Raj:)With all that helium in you,
you're lucky you don't float away.
(Leonard:)Are you really admitting defeat?
(Sheldon:)-I never admit defeat.
-Good.
(Sheldon:)However, on an unrelated topic,
I'm never getting out of this bed again.
(Leonard:)What if you could make Kripke
look even sillier than he made you look?
(Raj:)-I don't think that's possible.
-You're not helping.
(Raj:)I didn't come to help. I came to mock.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, what you need to do...
(Leonard:)...is figure out a way
to exact vengeance on Kripke, like....
(Leonard:)Like how the Joker got back at Batman...
(Leonard:)...for putting him in the Arkham Asylum
for the Criminally Insane.
He didn't stay and talk about his feelings
with the other villains.